The Observer Records UA062
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Observer negatives, 1972 -- 1989; 1980 -- 1989; UA062.004; 2.65 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s)
  - Arena Theater, 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00005 (Box 9)
    Androcles the Lion (A-B): 10/19/83, Ken McGagh; Arena Theater: 11/26/82, A. Levenson; Began on Horseback: 1/30/85, Dan Thornton; Began on Horseback: 1/30/85, Dan Thornton; ECK/Abbot/ Arena (A-C): 2/26/80, John Warhu?; Tufts Arena Theater; Uncle Vanya (A-B): 12/5/84, Dan Thornton; Chris Arnold Dahepon: 2/27/84, Ken McGagh; Chicago: 10/84, Dan Thornton; Chicago: 11/84, Dan Thornton.
  - Arena Theater, 1983; UA062.004.009.00006 (Box 9)
    Exit the King (A-B): Nov. 2, L Wong; Gypsy: 11/17/83, Ken Mabash
  - Arts, 1981 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00007 (Box 9)
    Armenian Art Professor (A-B): 2/28/84, Dan Thornton; Proposed Ad for Art Grant (A-B): 4/4/84, Ann Sherpick; Artist in Residence (A-B): 3/22/83, Ken McGagh; Buildings & Bombs/Artist in Residence: 3/8/87, Ken McGagh; Medford Art Show: 9/14/83, Lisa Wong; Art Show: 9/16/81, Joel Barhsak.
  - Arts House, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00008 (Box 9)
    Arts House Exhibit: 2/20/85, Dan Thornton; Art Center: 2/29/86, Chuck Boatwright; Arts House-Jay Wecht: 3/6/85, Dan Thornton
  - (B), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00009 (Box 9)
    Boston Garden: 9/1/82, A. Levenson; Bay Bank: 3/3/82, Ken McGagh; Bay Bank Rip Set Eaton (?): 9/1;Bridge (A-C):10/14/82, Karen E.; Beezlebubs:10/20/82, Izeman; Boston Night From Library Roof (A-C):3/3/82, A. Levenson; Bunker Hill (A-C): 7/3/82, A. Levenson; Bus 96 to Harvard (A-B): 3/10/82, A. Levenson; Bear Drinkers, Scoot, Tory, Etc.: 5/5/82, A. Levenson.
  - (B), 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00010 (Box 9)
    Gum: 10/14/82, A. Levenson; Bookstore and Manager: 9/1, R. Lipset; Bum: 3/8/83, A. Levenson; Sweet Hall- Bursar's Office: 2/2/82, J.B. Lyon.
  - Baseball (Men), 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00011 (Box 9)
    Men's Baseball (A-B): 4/7/84, Dan Thornton; Baseball: 4/9/84, Ken McGagh; Baseball Training: 3/28/84, Dan Thornton; Baseball (A-B): 4/10/84, Dan Thornton; Baseball- Maso Bay?: 4/28/81, Karen Edensword; Baseball and Samto (A-B): 5/5/82, A Levenson; Baseball Coach John Casey: 3/28/84, Dan Thornton; Baseball (A-B): 3/83, Armin Seifart
  - Baseball (Men) and Softball (Women), 1985; UA062.004.009.00012 (Box 9)
    Baseball and Women's Softball (A-D): 4/10/85, Ken McGagh; Baseball and Women's Softball: 4/10/85, Ken McGagh (3 sheets).
  - Baseball, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00013 (Box 9)
    Baseball: 4/11/85, Ken McGagh; Baseball (A-B): 4/16/86, Sheryl Kalls; Baseball (A-B): 4/23/86, Sheryl Kalls
  - Basketball (Men), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00014 (Box 9)
    Varsity Men's Basketball Practice(A-B): 2/2/83, Ken McGagh; Varsity Men's Basketball Coach John Whik: 2/2/83, McGagh; Men's Varsity Basketball: 1/31/80, Sohn Marlin; Basketball vs. Fitchburg; Men's Basketball Tufts vs. Le Moune: 2/4/80, Rob Tuleot; Men's Basketball- Brandeis(A-C): 2/11/80, Rob Tuleot; Men's Basketball Merrimack: 1/26/80, Rob Tuleot; Men's Basketball (A-C): 11/17/82, Al Levenson; Men's Basketball: 1/23/85, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball: 11/23/85, Ken McGagh; Basketball: Ethan McMaher; Men's Basketball: 2/9/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball: 2/7/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball (A-B): 2/2/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball (A-C): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball (A-C): 11/10/83, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball: 2/23/83, Allen Levenson; Men's Basketball: 1/23/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Basketball: 1/23/85, Ken McGagh; Basketball Cousen's (A-B): 1/26/82, Al Levenson.
  - Men's Basketball, 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00015 (Box 9)
    Men's Basketball Practice: 1/28/86, D.Tan; Men's Hoop vs. Brandeis (A-C): 2/10/82, A. Levenson
  - Basketball (Women), 1981 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00016 (Box 9)
    Basketball (Women) (A-B): 12/2/81, Allen; Women's Basketball (A-B): 3/83, Armin Seifart; Girl's Basketball: 2/2/84, E. Puiver; Girl's Basketball (A-B): 1/27/82, A. Levenson; Girl's Basketball: 3/9/83, A. Levenson; Women's Basketball: 2/13/85, Ken McGagh; Women's Varsity Basketball:, John Marlin; Women's Basketball: 3/9/83, Ken McGagh; Women's Basketball (A-C): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh; Women's Basketball (A-B): 1/26/84, Ken McGagh; Women's Basketball: 1/26/84, Ken McGagh; Women's Basketball: 2/13/85, Ken McGagh; Women's Basketball/ Women's Eastern Nazae?: 1/28, Rob Tyler; Women's Basketball (A-C): 12/8/82, Ken McGagh
  - Women's Basketball, 1986; UA062.004.009.00017 (Box 9)
    Female Hoops (A-C): 2/86; Women's Basketball (A-B): 1/23/86
  - (C), 1980 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00018 (Box 9)
    Somerville Kids (A-C): 9/80; Counseling Center: 2/1/83, Izeman; Conservatory Students (A-C): 11/2, L. Wong; Clothes by Mark Florence: 11/16; Counseling Center: 12/9/81, Allen Levenson; USS Constitution (A-B): 2/3/80, A. Levenson; T Construction: 4/22/81, Karen Edensword; Constructive Conversation (A-C): 9/15/83, Paul Fold; Concentration Camp Speaker: 4/27/82, Allen Levenson; Student Catering: 2/8/84, Dan Thornton; Construction- Cabot, Medford Dorm: 1/10/80, Karen Edensword; Jonathan Edwards Concert (A-B): 3/11, Marlin; Chinatown: 12/9/83, Stephen Morisseau.
  - (C), 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00019 (Box 9)
    Cuban and African Lecture: 11/15/52, Ken McGagh; Christmas Tree Lighting (A-C): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh; Careers Fair (A-C): 2/23/84, Ken McGagh; Circus: 10/30/82, Al Levenson; Crime: 2/23/84, Al Levenson; Citizen Participation, Draft Activist: Carolyn Hines; Creative (Creatine?) Anachronism (A-C): 11/11/83, Ken McGagh.
  - (C), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00020 (Box 9)
    Condom Dispenser: 9/28/87, Steve Bushell; Cukoo's Nest with Workers: 4/9/86, Sheryl Kalls; China Town: 2/10/87, Steven Bushell; Coffee Cups: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright
  - Cabot, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00021 (Box 9)
    CCO (A-C): 10/14/82, Chris Hoffman; Calendar: 4/10/84, Dan Thornton.
  - Campaign for Tufts, UA062.004.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Campus, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00023 (Box 9)
    First Snow (A-B): 10/9/81, Allen Levenson; Little Kids and Campus Shots (A-C): 4/6/83, Ken McGagh; 48 Professor's Row: 1980, Karen Edensword; Calander Stuff (A-B): 10/25, Lisa Wong; Calander (A-B): 11/2, L. Wong; Fall 82 (A-C): Rick Lipset; Things on Campus: 9/15/82, Al Levenson.
  - Campus, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00024 (Box 9)
    Cannon: 11/17/82, Steve Morrisseau; Campus Snow Shots: 2/2/84, Ken McGagh; Campus Shots: 4/7/83, Ken McGagh; Campus Shots (A-C): 9/8/83, Ken McGagh; Campus Shots (A-C): 3/15/83; Cooler: 3/8/83, A. Levenson; Campus Shots: 4/6/81, Ken McGagh; Night Campus Shots (A-C): 4/7/83, Ken McGagh; Campus: 4/13/82, A. Levenson; Campus Shots: Ken McGagh; Campus Shots-Fall Foliage: 11/7/83, Ken McGagh; Campus Shots (A-B): 2/17/84, Ken McGagh; Campus Shots-Fall Foliage: 10/19/83, Ken McGagh
  - Campus, 1985 -- 1989; UA062.004.009.00025 (Box 9)
    Goddard (A-B): 12/4/86, Steven Bushell; Goddard Chapel (A-B): 11/25/86, Steven Bushell; Hooper House: 2/19/86, Julia Gordon; Professor's Row (A-B): 1/26/87?, Al Levenson; Ballou Hall with a big hole in front of it: 10/24/87, Steve Bushell; 92 Professor's Row: 3/27/85, Dan Thornton; 4 Capen St.: 12/3/89, Joseph Bushell; Artsy Fartsy: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Gloria & TCU: 10/1/85, Chuck; Artsy Fartsy: 9/23/87, Eliza Eagle
  - Campus Center, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00026 (Box 9)
    Campus Center (A-B): 8/31/83, Ken McGagh; Campus Center (A-B): 2/9/84, Ken McGagh; Campus Center (A-B): 4/5/84, Ken McGagh; Campus Ctr (A-B): 4/5/84, Ken McGagh; Campus Center/ Brown House:, KM; Campus Shots: 9/21/83, Mark Florence; Joke Campus Tour (A-B): 3/10/82, Al Levenson; Where Brave House Was Shown?: Kalis; Campus Center: 4/21/83, Ken McGagh
  - Campus Center, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00027 (Box 9)
    Stage 2 Campus Center: 3/9/87, Steven Bushell; New Addition to Campus Center (A-B): 1/27/87, Chuck Boatwright; Plot of Land behind Campus Center: 3/26/86, Chuck Boatwright; Campus Center Plus: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Tufts Campus (A-B): 2/12/87, Steven Bushell
  - Capen House Demonstration, 1981; UA062.004.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Carmichael, 1982; UA062.004.009.00029 (Box 9)
    Blacks Eating Dinner at Carmichael: 2/24/82, Allen Levenson; Carmichael (A-B); Carmichael Construction (A-B): 9/11, R. Lipset; Carmichael: 3/22/82, Jack Ruderman
  - Charles, 1982; UA062.004.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Chemistry, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00031 (Box 9)
    Chemistry Vent: 2/29/84, Denise Letzer; Chemistry Hood: 2/29/84, Denise Letzer; American Chemistry Society (A-B): 4/5/84; Chemistry Lab (A-C): 9/5/83, Ken McGagh
  - Chemistry, 1984 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00032 (Box 9)
    Chemistry People: 10/30/87, Tina Daley; Chemistry Lab (A-B): 2/23/84, Ken McGagh; Ominous Pictures of the Chemistry Building: 9/87; Chemistry explosion: 12/4/86, Steven Bushell
  - Chorale, 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00033 (Box 9)
    Tufts Chorale: 4/28/83, Ken McGagh; Chorale: 10/1/82, Allen Levenson
  - Clambake, 1982; UA062.004.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Cohen, 1980 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00035 (Box 9)
    Cohen Renovations: 11/80, Karen Edensword; Cohen (A-C): 9/23/87, Eliza Eagle; Cohen (A-B): 10/28/87, Steve Bushell, Cohen (A-B): 1/27/87, Chuck Boatwright
  - Commencement, 1982; UA062.004.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Computer, 1981; UA062.004.009.00037 (Box 9)
    Vasilio
  - Cousens Gym, 1982; UA062.004.009.00038 (Box 9)
    Cousen's Pre-Renovation; Cousens Gym: Ken McGagh
  - Crew, 1983; UA062.004.009.00039 (Box 9)
    Brad Shots Hamilton
  - Crew, 1987; UA062.004.009.00040 (Box 9)
    Rowing Team Fundraiser: 10/8, Chris Mowagle; Crew: 9/6/87, Steve Bushell
  - Men's Cross Country, 1982; UA062.004.009.00041 (Box 9)
    Rick Lipse
  - Cross Country, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00042 (Box 9)
    Women's cross-country: Chris Davita; Men's and Women's cross-country (A-B): 9/14/83, Ken McGagh; Cross-country, Men's: 10/23/85, Chuck Boatwright
  - CSL, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00043 (Box 9)
    CSL: 3/2/81, Charyl Hart; CSL Meeting, Don Klesn (A-B): 9/23/81, Allen Levenson; Noam Chomsky: 4/80, Bob Cohen; CSL: 2/20/81, Karen Edensword; CSL Meeting: 3/3/83, Izeman; CSL: 2/8/84, Dan Thornton; CSL Meeting (A-B): 11/17/82, Ken McGagh; CSL Meeting: 12/9/82, Izeman; CSL (A-B): 10/19/81, A. Balonon; CSL (A-B): 9/22/82, Allen Levenson; CSL (A-C): 3/22/82, Jack Rudeman
  - CSL, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00044 (Box 9)
    CSL Meeting: 2/10/87, Steven Bushell; CSL Meeting: 3/5/86, Sheryl Kalis; CSL Meeting: 4/10/86, Sheryl Kalis; CSL: 4/7/87, Steven Bushell; CSL Meeting: 3/4/87, Jason Goodrick; John Darcy and CSL: 9/86, Stephanie Wolk
  - Cup and Saucer, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00045 (Box 9)
    Cup and Saucer: The Interview (A-C): 11/17/83, M. Slash; Cup and Saucer (A-C): 4/5/84, Ken McGagh; Cup and Saucer (A-B): 4/2/84, Ken McGagh; Wright's Cup and Saucer (A-B): 11/4/81, Karen Edensword; (?): 3/9/82, Allen Levenson
  - (D), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00046 (Box 9)
    Atam Snack Bar: 10/12/83, B Rigby; Obscene Phone Callers (A-B): 2/24/82, Allen Levenson; Out at Sea: 11/17/82, Izeman; Oxfam-18 (A-B): 11/10/81, J. Krough
  - (D), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00047 (Box 9)
    Drinking Games: 10/13/83?; Daily Editor in Chief: 10/12, Lisa Wong; Diploma: 11/6/83, Al Levenson; Drugs in NFL Lecture: 3/6/84, E. Pulver
  - (D), 1985 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00048 (Box 9)
    Our Wonderful Darkroom: 85, Chuck Boatwright; Lunch Room: 10/30/87, Susan Apler; Democratiz-Socialist Meeting
  - Dance, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00049 (Box 9)
    Jack Donn, 28 Sawyer (A-C): 3/28/81; Dance (A-B): 4/28/81, Karen Edensword; 3 Dancers-In Arena: 9/80, Karen Edensword; Dance Concert, coreography by Susan Sachs?: 11/15/81, K. Edensword; Shotty Dorm: 3/9/83, Al Levenson; Dance Practice (A-C): 11/82, Armin Seifart; Tufts Beach, Mira Cantor, Dance, Gallery II (A-C): Armin Seifart; Dance (A-C): 1980, Karen Edensword; Dance Week (A-B): 9/21/83, Ken McGagh; Dance Week (A-B): 10/5, Lisa Wong; Dance Armour? (A-C): 11/17/83, Ken McGagh; Dance: 11/15/81; Unlabeled
  - Dance Marathon, 1983 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00050 (Box 9)
    Dance Marathon (A-C): 3/1/84, Ken McGagh; Dance Marathon: 2/28/84, Dan Thornton; Dance Marathon: 2/27/85; Dance Marathon: 2/27/85, Dan Thornton; Dance Marathon: 3/2/83
  - Davis Square, 1983; UA062.004.009.00051 (Box 9)
    Davis Square MBTA (A-C): 9/26/83, Ken McGagh; Davis Square (A-C); Eric Sagermdin?, Professor Schl?, Davis Square Fire (A-B): Carolyn Hine
  - Davis Square, 1987; UA062.004.009.00052 (Box 9)
    Davis Third Rail: 9/10/87, Steve Bushell; Davis Square T Stop (A-C): 10/1, Jib Wilkinson
  - Dining Halls, 1979 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00053 (Box 9)
    Dewick (A-C): 2/24/82, Al Levenson; Dining Halls (A-C): 12/1/83, Ken McGagh; Dining Services(A-C): 1979/1980, Karen Edensword; Working in Dining Halls (A-C): 3/17/84, Ann Sherpick
  - Dormitories, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00054 (Box 9)
    IDC: 3/81, K. Edensword; Dorm Duty: 9/15/82, Al Levenson; Carpenter (Wierd Room, Ozone) (A-C): 2/13/84, Dan Thornton
  - Drier Sit-In, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00055 (Box 9)
    Sit-In: 5/5/83, Al Levenson; Bob Cohen, Peter Drier: 4/80; Peter Drier: 4/83, R. Lipset; Mayer, Crowds?, Peter Drier: 4/83, Rick Lipset
  - (E), 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00056 (Box 9)
    Tufts Early Music Ensemble: 11/17, Stephen Morisseau; European Center (A-B): 3/3/83, Ken McGagh; EY8?; Ec. Class: 10/13/82, Al Levenson; Eighty's (A-B): 10/21/82, Al Levenson; Encore: 11/17/82, Al Levenson; Eidovul? Jeeman?: 1/26/83
  - (E), 1984 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00057; Bushnell, Steven (Box 9)
    Equestrian Team; PBS Ad: 1/27/87, Chuck Boatwright; Etcetera Page: 4/5/84, Ken McGagh; Espresso Pizza Man (A-B): 2/3/86, Chuck Boatwright On January 3, 2013, DCA staff added additional negatives taken by Steven Bushnell (accession 2013.061).
  - Eaton, 1987; UA062.004.009.00058 (Box 9)
    Eaton User Area (A-B): 2/10/87, Ejyo Kataguri; Construction in Eaton
  - Elderly, 1982; UA062.004.009.00059 (Box 9)
    Elderly Meeting (A-B): Allen Levenson
  - (F), 1979 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00060 (Box 9)
    Fall Fling, Livingston Taylor: 9/7/81, Joel; Dumpster Fire (A-B): 4/14/85, Ken McGagh; Freshperson (Dumb and Bewildered): 2/8/84, Dan Thornton; Final Exams: 1/26/84, Ken McGagh; Supplement FBI-CIA Documents (A-B): 10/27, K.E.; Fletcher: 9/21/83, Lisa Wong; Fenway: 7/1/82, Allen Levenson; Firedrill at Medical Center: 2/10/82, Al Levenson; Franzeen (A-B): 9/8/82; Freshman Life (A-B): 11/30, Mark Florence; Fence: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Fire in Teale Square: 2/79; Fireworks: 11/4/83, Ken McGagh; First Day: 9/1/82, Al Levenson
  - (F), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00061 (Box 9)
    Unlabeled: 4/23/86, Stephanie Wolk; Frisbee Throwers: 9/10/87, Steve Bushell
  - Faculty and Staff (mixed up), 1984; UA062.004.009.00062 (Box 9)
  - Faculty and Staff (mixed up), 1984 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00063 (Box 9)
  - Faculty and Staff (mixed up), 1984 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00064 (Box 9)
    Faculty '85 #5 Rebecca Fleweling, Scot Flarherty, Professor Rob Houster; Faculty '84 #6
  - Faculty and Staff (A), 1979 -- 1980; UA062.004.009.00065 (Box 9)
    T.J. Anderson (A-B): 2/80, Marlin; T.J. Anderson (A-B): 1979, Karen Edensword; Colcoran, T.J. Anderson, Shaefer, Gibson, Dfrizzoni.
  - Staff and Faculty (A), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.004.009.00066 (Box 9)
    Anderson (A-B): 10/6/87, Sheryl Kalls; Admisssions Prospective Students: 1980, Karen Edensword; Teach-in Todatoshi Akiba: 11/11/81, A. Balowon
  - Faculty and Staff (B), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00067 (Box 9)
    Dean Behnke: 11/27/82, A Levenson; Betsy Bowden: 4/4/79; Eric Brass: 2/8/84, Paul Fulni; Jan Ballon: 4/21/82, A. Levenson; Behnke: 8/1/82, A. Levenson; Michael Benke(?) (A-C); Behnke: 8/1/82, Al Levenson; Barbara Braithwaite: 9/1980, Karen Edensword; Professor Dale Brown: 3/6/85, Dan Thornton; Curtis Barnes: 9/1/80, Al Levenson; Kathy Baker (A-B): 3/28/84, Ann Sherpick; Hugo Bedau: 11/4/81, Alma Baconon; Bernheim's: 4/13/82, A. Levenson; Knable, Behnke: Keith Bryant; Sylven Barnet (A-B): 10/14/81, Allen Levenson.
  - Faculty and Staff (B), 1984 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00068 (Box 9)
    Tony Brown (A-B): 2/29/84, Ann Sherpick; Kathy Baker SAO: 10/31/86, Steven Bushell; Kathy Baker (A-B): 3/4/86, Ejyo Kataguri; Daniel Brown: 10/1/86, Steph Wolk; Kathleen Bebe: Boatwright; Kathy Watson-Baker: 12/5/84, Dan Thornton; Peggy Barrett: 1/27/87, Chuck Boatwright; Biology Professor; Unlabeled: 2/12/86, Julia Gordon
  - Staff and Faculty (C), 1980 -- 1982; UA062.004.009.00069 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 1 of 7, 1980-09-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00001 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 2 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00002 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 3 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00003 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 4 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00004 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 5 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00005 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 6 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00006 (Box 9)
    - Grant Curtis 7 of 7, 1982-12-01; UA062.004.009.00069.00007 (Box 9)
  - Faculty and Staff (C), 1984 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00070 (Box 9)
    Rabbi Cushman?: 3/8/84, Ken McGagh; Camora: 4/7/87 Chuck Boatwright; Collera: 2/10/87, Chuck Boatwright; Cuttino: 9/3/86, Steven Bushell; Callow: 11/20, Brad the Editor; Sherwood Collin: 10/30/87, Tina Daley; Pictures of Dean Cuttino: Steven Bushell; Dean Colcord: 2/5/86, S. Wolk; Dean Colcord: 3/4/86, Ejyo Kataguri
  - Staff and Faculty (D), 1981 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00071 (Box 9)
    Didio: Stephen Morisseau; Virginia Drachman (A-B): 10/17/84, Dan Thornton; Professor Daniels: 4/1/81, Sherpick; J. Dirgle Trig?: 4/13/82, A. Levenson; Professor Delphina: 2/24/82, Allen Levenson; Rev. Drooches: 9/20/82, Ann Sherpick; Professor Dennett: 10/19/81, Allen Levenson; Nancy Dietz (A-B): 11/84, Dan Thornton; Steve Dennis: 2/3/82, Al Levenson; Jeanne Dillon: 10/84, Dan Thornton; Durgin: 12/9/81, Allen Levenson; Professor Jeanne Dillon: 9/14/82, Nasrallah Walid; Jeanne Dillon: 3/13/85?, Ken McGagh; Dr. Russel Deburlo: Dan Thornton
  - Faculty and Staff (D), 1987; UA062.004.009.00072 (Box 9)
    John Darcy: Boatwright
  - Faculty and Staff (E), 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00073 (Box 9)
    Professor Elias Political Science: 10/27/82, Izeman; David Elkin (E.P.); Edelman (?): 5/5/82, A. Levenson; Dean Evans (A-C): 2/17/84, Ken McGagh; Eastwood, Registrar (?): 1/27/82, A. Levenson; Mildred Eastwood: 7/1/82, A. Levenson; Laughter and Dr. Edelin: 2/83, Armin Seifart
  - Faculty and Staff (E), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00074 (Box 9)
    Eastwood: 3/8/87, Steven Bushell; Adelman: 3/4/86, Julia Gordon; Another Boooring Economics Guy who only had 4 people at his lecture: 10/29/87, Steve Bushell; Some Economics guy that had only 4 people at his miserable lecture: 10/29/87, Steve Bushell; Director of International Center; Unlabeled (A-B): 11/12/86, Chuck Boatwright; Shelly Emerson: 12/3/86, Chuck Boatwright; Professor Elliot, Dean Maxwell: 10/2, Brad Bernstein; Roberto Eisemann: 2/11/87, Chuck Boatwright
  - Staff, Faculty, and Students (F), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00075 (Box 9)
    John Fulginiti: 1/30/85, Ken McGagh; Jodie Freeman, Ted Rosenthal: 9/21/83, Carole Levenson; Tom Frank, Telefund Operator (A-B): 4/81, K. Edensword; Finney (A-B): 4/21/82, A. Levenson; Feinlieb: 10/27/82, Izeman; Sargeant Foster TUPD: 3/15/83, Ken McGagh; Barney Frank: 10/14/82, Allen Levenson; Barney Frank (A-C): 2/10/82, Allen Levenson; Feinlieb: 9/1/82, Al Levenson; Sargeant Flaherty; Father Foley: 9/13/82, Nasrallah Walid; Rebecca Flewelling: 10/19/81, Allen Levenson; Folch-Pi: 4/81, C. Hine; Mason Spernold: 4/27/82, Al Levenson; Faraz: 11/30, L. Wong; Libby Fulgione, Michael Bialeas (A-B): 1/2/85, Chris Monagle; Melissa Fernel: 10/27/82, A. Levenson; Roberta Flewelling: 9/80, Karen Edensword; Lee Miranda, Society of Women Engineers: 10/12, Lisa Wong
  - Faculty and Staff (F), 1986; UA062.004.009.00076 (Box 9)
    Sgrt. Flaherty: 3/26/86, Alison Ferante; Chairwoman Fine Arts Department: 3/26/86, Alison Ferante; Unlabeled (A-B): 1/29/86, Chuck Boatwright; Sargeant Flaherty Tufts Police: 10/17/86, Steven Bushell
  - Staff and Faculty, Students (G), 1981 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00077 (Box 9)
    Golf Coach Bill Gehling (A-B): 3/15/85, Ken McGagh; Professor Gantalick: 3/8/84, Ken McGagh; Gibson in Class (A-B): 3/81, Karen Edensword; Gelber: 9/9/82, A. Levenson; Allan Gelber: 1/26/83, Deman; Professor Goldstein: 11/83, B. Rigby; Lest. Gelb: 3/17/82, A. Levenson; C-6: Stephen Morrisseau; Steve Guessing; Professor Greenwald: Nov. 2, L. Wore?; Fernanda Gordon: 9/17/86, Sheryl Kalus; R. Gelling Golf Coach: 4/13/82, A. Levenson; Curtis Grant, Financial Aid (A-B): 9/3/81, Karen; Galantic (A-B): 9/81/82; Judy Glavin: Nora McTierman; Cuban Crisis at JFK with Gibson: 10/27/82, Allen Levenson; Caroline Grossman (A-B): 10/6/82, Rick Lipsey
  - Faculty and Staff (G), 1986; UA062.004.009.00078 (Box 9)
    Prof. Guterman; Sol Gittleman: 3/4/86, Ejyo Kataguri; Sol Gittleman: 1/28/86, Ellen Sackelman, Soviet Dissident on Detector Ging-Bing or whatever his name is: 10/31/88, Steven Bushell
  - Staff and Faculty (H), 1981 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00079 (Box 9)
    Professor Haviland: 10/28/81, K. Edensword; Captain Holland: 12/1/81, Allen Levenson; Harleston (A-B); H-16: 1/28/81; Pro. Hamilton: 3/26/86, Sheryl Kalib; Howard Hunter (A-B): 9/29/81, Karen Edensword; Ken Hall and Jason: 10/13/82, Al Levenson; Astronaut Rick Hauk: 2/20/85, Dan Thornton; Handicapped Production: 4/14/83, Ken McGagh; Gordon Handicapped Person: A. Levenson; H-15 (A-B): S. Morisseau; Hadlock: 3/9/83, A. Levenson; Professor Hardar: 11/2/83, Mark Florence; Loose unlabeled negatives; Professors Luria, Marrone, Drier, Slapikoff: C. Hine
  - Faculty and Staff (H), 1984 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00080 (Box 9)
    Houston Hall: 3/25/87, Steven Bushell; Director African American: 2/7/86, Chuck Boatwright; Father Hunt (A-C)
  - Staff and Faculty (J and K), 1983 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00081 (Box 9)
    Mary Ann Jacobs (A-B): 10/16/86, Sheryl Kalis; Mary Lee Jacobs: 3/5/86, Sheryl Kalis; Teach-In Sheldon Kroninsky: A. Balowon; Tim Knap-Headshots Anthropology Dept.: 9/21/83, Lisa Wong
  - Staff and Faculty (K), 1980 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00082 (Box 9)
    Police Chief Kerney (A-B): 3/3/83, Ken McGagh; Chief Kierney: 10/81, A. Levenson; Kirshner (A-B): 11/3/82, Armin Seifart; Bobbie Knable (A-B): 9/22/82, Rick Lipset; Bobbie Knable (A-B): 10/84, Dan Thornton; Bobby Knable, Dean of Students, 9/8/81, Karen Edensword; Bobby Knable Outside Ballou: 10/19/81, Karen Edensword; Bobby Knable Baking Apple Pie: 11/13/80, Allen Levenson; Captain Kearny, Tufts P.D.; Bobby Knable: 3/81, Karen Edensword; Bobby Knable, Dean of Students: 9/18/81, K. Edensword
  - Faculty and Staff (L), 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.009.00083 (Box 9)
    Levine, Poetry Reading (A-B): 9/28/82, Izeman; Professor Laurent: 9/15/82, Nasrallah Walid; Larry Ladd: 8/28/81, Cathy Watson, Karen Edensword; Professor Laurent (History) (A-B): 2/23/82, Karen Sotiropoulos; Larry Lad's Baby: 12/8/82, Ken McGagh; Pierre Laurant: 1982, Ken McGagh; Pierre Laurant: 2/13/82, Ken McGagh, Director of Newspaper at Lincoln Filene Center: Stuart Langton.
  - Faculty and Staff, Students (L), 1982; UA062.004.009.00084 (Box 9)
    Unlabeled negatives; Mara and Lowenstein: A Levenson
  - Staff and Faculty (L), 1987; UA062.004.009.00085 (Box 9)
    Zela Luria: Celia; Lunch Lady: Susan Adler
  - Staff and Faculty, Students (M), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00086 (Box 9)